adam4adam.com 2019-12-03

# Privacy Policy – Adam4Adam

**Effective date 25 May 2018**

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**1) Scope of Privacy Policy**

The Adam4Adam Privacy Policy may be found below. In this Privacy Policy, we describe the information that we collect about you, that you provide to us and will be processed by us as you use our website, mobile apps and other services. Your use of the Adam4Adam Site and services constitutes your acceptance of the terms and conditions of the Adam4Adam Privacy Policy, of our recently updated User Agreement and of the Adam4Adam Community Guidelines. You are responsible for reviewing and becoming familiar with all of these terms.

A4A Network Inc. has created this privacy policy because we value our members and recognize their right to keep personal information private. This statement discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the World Wide Web site located at www.Adam4Adam.com (the "Adam4Adam Site"), mobile apps and other services. We believe very strongly that private information should remain private. We'd like to hear your feedback about this statement. If you have comments or questions, please Contact Us.

Except as otherwise expressly discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are other members of the Site or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them.

**2) Information we collect and how we use it**

Cookies

Our Web site sets cookies to administer our site, to gather broad demographic information, to deliver content requested by you or specific to your interests, to customize our Web site for you, and to save your username and city so that you don't have to enter it each time you visit.

A cookie is a small line of data that is stored on your hard drive. Some cookies are only stored for the duration of a single browser session; others persist across sessions. We only save your password and member name if you tell us to do so; your password is encrypted, stored on your computer and transferred over the Internet in an encrypted format. Keep in mind that anyone using your Web browser would be able to access the Adam4Adam Site as you if you choose to store your member name and password. Adam4Adam's Web servers also set session ID cookies that are used to allow our servers to deliver information you request (e.g., search results). Members who do not want to receive cookies can instruct their Web browsers to refuse them; however, doing so may prevent most parts of Adam4Adam's site from working (e.g., anything that requires login, including member chat, etc). While cookies set by Adam4Adam may be used to collect personally identifiable information and can be traced to an individual user, this personally identifiable information is used only for internal purposes.

Registration Form

Membership on the Adam4Adam Site is completely optional. Adam4Adam's registration form requires users to give their email address. On our join form, required fields are marked. Adam4Adam will never share e-mail addresses with third party organizations without your express permission.

Control of Your Password

Do not disclose your password to any third parties nor share it with any third parties. If you lose control of your password, you may lose control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. To change your password you can do so at any time through the MY ACCOUNT page then click Change Password.

Order Forms

When purchasing products or services on the Adam4Adam site, you're asked for credit card, billing, and shipping information. This information is transmitted using a secure, encrypted form. You can see that the transaction is secure from the fact that the URL begins with the secure address https:// and we ensure encryption through the use of standard SSL encryption technologies. This credit card information is gathered to bill customers for services purchased. Only billing vendors have access to financial information and only for the purpose of billing customers. At times Adam4Adam may refer users to other Web sites to purchase products or services. User activity on those sites is covered by the privacy policies on those sites.

Community Tools

Adam4Adam provides many venues for member interaction and community. In some cases use of such tools (e.g., chat rooms) may reveal a user's member name or e-mail address and may permit users to publish certain personal information on the Adam4Adam Site. In all cases, users affirmatively choose to expose or place this information in public areas (e.g. profile page) of the Adam4Adam Site, and thereby agree that such information may be viewed by or forwarded to anyone. Users who do not want this information to be publicly available should not post in public areas of the Adam4Adam Site.

Adam4Adam Profiles and ProAds

Adam4Adam permits users to submit adult-oriented personal information for use in the Adam4Adam Profile and ProAd services. This information is also stored for the purposes of member self-publishing and interaction and to customize the user's Adam4Adam site experience. By registering for Adam4Adam Profiles or ProAd and submitting your user information, you understand that the information provided in the profie or ProAd, including your photograph, may be forwarded by members to other members and to persons who are not members. Adam4Adam will not knowingly collect Profile or ProAd information from those under the age of 18.

Member Feedback

Adam4Adam stores feedback members send to us. This feedback is used to administer and refine the Adam4Adam Site and associated services and at times may be shared with Adam4Adam partners either in aggregate form or individually with specific identifying characteristics about the Member (e.g., e-mail address or name) removed.

IP Addresses

Adam4Adam tracks individual IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our service, to administer our site and to gather broad demographic information. User IP address information is used only for our internal purposes. 

**3) When and why we share information**

Adam4Adam reserves the right to share some or all of your personal information with its parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures or other companies under common control with Adam4Adam, in which case Adam4Adam will require such entities to honor this privacy policy. If Adam4Adam is acquired by another company, that company will obtain the member information collected by Adam4Adam and will assume the rights and obligations set forth in this privacy policy regarding that information.

Notwithstanding anything else in this policy, Adam4Adam may also disclose personal and aggregate information when required by a valid legal mechanism such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order, or when we deem it necessary, in our sole discretion, to protect our rights and the safety of others, or our members, employees, or properties.

Adam4Adam believes that members' private communications in chat rooms, e-mail, and instant message-like conversations should generally remain confidential. Adam4Adam does not disclose private communications unless ordered to do so through a valid legal mechanism such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order, to protect the company's rights and property, or during emergencies when we believe safety is at risk. Please remember that what you write or post in public areas such as chat rooms and message boards is available to all Adam4Adam members, and in many cases other visitors to the Adam4Adam site. Also keep in mind that Adam4Adam is not responsible for what other users may do with private communications you've had with them. While chat and instant message-like conversations pass through Adam4Adam's servers, we do not store logs of these conversations.

**4) Your rights and choices**

OFF-SITE LINKS

Adam4Adam provides links to other sites. Adam4Adam is not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of these other sites.

OPT-OUT

Our site provides users the opportunity upon registration to opt out of receiving communications from us and from our partners, affiliates, and advertisers. These options are available during registration, and through the notification setting on the MY ACCOUNT page. Please note that even if you have chosen to opt out of receiving communications from us, we reserve the right to contact you by e-mail about material changes to this privacy policy or the Adam4Adam User Agreement.

**5) Delete information**

Adam4Adam gives users the following options for removing their information from our database:

  1. Towards the bottom of the MY ACCOUNT page click on the Delete Account link and follow the instruction provided.
  2. You can send e-mail to support@Adam4Adam.com. Please be sure to include your name, username, and e-mail address.

Adam4Adam gives users the following options for changing or modifying information previously provided: In the MY ACCOUNT page user info can be changed in the "Edit My Profile" page and photos can be uploaded or deleted in the "Upload My Photo" page.

**6) Security**

Adam4Adam implements reasonable security measures to help protect your data from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access. However, no physical or electronic securitysystem is impenetrable, but all information you provide to us is stored on secured servers.

We can’tguarantee the security of the Service's servers or databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet and any transmission is at your own risk.

We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

**7) Changes to Policy**

We may update this policy from time to time. If we make any significant changes to the way in which we treat your personal information, we will inform you of such changes via e-mail or by posting a notice on the Adam4Adam site. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please feel free to Contact Us.

**8) How you can access your personal information**

You can access some of the personal information that we collect about you by logging in to your account. You also have the right to make a request to access other personal information we hold about you and to request corrections of any errors in that data

**9) Information about children**

Our services are not available to anyone who is not at least 18 years of age. If you are not at least 18 years of age, you are not permitted to become a Member or use our services.

**10) Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please feel free to Contact Us. 

Adam4Adam – A4A Network Inc Privacy Policy - Effective date 25 May 2018
